<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Bozo Mode]]></title><description><![CDATA[I write about development and music!]]></description><link>https://alyssaphacker.com</link><image><url>https://alyssaphacker.com/icon.png</url><title>Bozo Mode</title><link>https://alyssaphacker.com</link></image><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 23:58:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alyssaphacker.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><copyright><![CDATA[2022 Justin Kristensen]]></copyright><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><managingEditor><![CDATA[glitchedcoder@gmail.com]]></managingEditor><webMaster><![CDATA[glitchedcoder@gmail.com]]></webMaster><ttl>60</ttl><item><title><![CDATA[Twelve Carat Toothache]]></title><description><![CDATA[<h2 id="bestsongs">Best Songs</h2>
<hr />
<h4 id="reputation">Reputation</h4>
<p>A piano ballad with very powerful vocals. Amazing transition into the next track. </p>
<h4 id="lemontree">Lemon Tree</h4>
<p>An acoustic and synth combo with an interesting vibrato and accented "better," almost country-accented? Certainly experimental, but I think it works. Powerful vocals and lyrics about everybody's life seeming sweet and his feeling sour.</p>
<h4 id="wrappedaroundyourfinger">Wrapped Around Your Finger</h4>
<p>An absolute banger on the album. When this was originally leaked I knew it was going to be good. Slightly repetitive, but it works really well. Best part is towards the end where the instrumental is cut, exposing Post's powerful vocals and the eventual building back up into the instrumental with a colorful synth.</p>
<h4 id="ilikeyouftdojacat">I Like You ft. Doja Cat</h4>
<p>After Post's track "Same Bitches" on <em>Beerbongs & Bentleys</em>, post talks about his current girlfriend, someone to ground him in the insanity. Very wispy and mellow track with a catchy chorus. Doja absolutely delivers her feature and makes the track an 11/10 for me. The pan flute near the end wraps this happier track up well.</p>
<h4 id="icannotbeftgunna">I Cannot Be ft. Gunna</h4>
<p>The opposite and duo to "I Like You," Post talks about the struggles of having a relationship. A trap-like instrumental with powerful and melodic vocals. Gunna does his part for his feature and even follows the melody in his former part but for the latter part ends up sounding like he just ran out of coke, but it could be stylistic. Overall, good track.</p>
<h4 id="lovehatelettertoalcoholftfleetfoxes">Love/Hate Letter to Alcohol ft. Fleet Foxes</h4>
<p>Intro and outro choir are heavenly. The instrumental with deep bass and drums with the choir make an absolute banger track.</p>
<h4 id="wastingangelsftthekidlaroi">Wasting Angels ft. The Kid LAROI</h4>
<p>Synth track absolutely drowned in reverb. Post's thoughts about where he's been and how far he's come gives the track an inspirational feel. I usually don't like much from Kid LAROI but he absolutely killed on this track. The choir in the middle to the end along with the buildup is, well, angelic. </p>
<h4 id="onerightnowfttheweeknd">One Right Now ft. The Weeknd</h4>
<p>Don't get me wrong, I love both the Weeknd and Post Malone, but the duo is amazingly underwhelming on this track. The song is good but it's not <em>great</em>. Nothing in particular really blew me away. The instrumental is good, with a bass acting as the main melody with hard drums.</p>
<h2 id="okaysongs">Okay Songs</h2>
<hr />
<h4 id="coopedupftroddyrich">Cooped Up ft. Roddy Rich</h4>
<p>An amazing track on its own. Roddy Rich absolutely fucks up the flow with his abysmal lyrics:</p>
<blockquote>
  <p>Shit.</p>
  <p>Gotta pull up.</p>
  <p>Pull up.</p>
  <p>Imma pull up.</p>
  <p>I pull up.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Absolutely garbage lyrics and flow, absolutely abysmal. This track was going to be on the Best Songs tier until this goofy goober lookin' ahhh tried to make the shittiest feature possible and won in a landslide. I cannot even fathom how Post took a listen and was like "yeah this shit is :fire:." This is even worse than Young Thug's feature on "Goodbyes". Absolutely irredeemable. Go back to your one hit wonder "The Box" you <em>eeh err</em> lookin mf.</p>
<h4 id="euthanasia">Euthanasia</h4>
<p>A good song with a simplistic instrumental. Nothing really stood out with this song, but nothing really made it bad either.</p>
<h4 id="whenimalone">When I'm Alone</h4>
<p>Good song with a typical drum and beat instrumental. Vocals were good but Post's falsetto on this track was a bit of a miss. </p>
<h4 id="waitingforamiracle">Waiting For A Miracle</h4>
<p>Slow song with a simple instrumental, piano chords. Post's vocals are drowning in reverb, but the lyrics are pretty good.</p>
<h4 id="newrecording12jan32020">New Recording 12, Jan 3, 2020</h4>
<p>A simple song with an acoustic instrumental w/ rough vocals from Post. An incredibly short track, only a minute and a half. Sounds like this was the inspiration for the album, given the date.</p>
<h2 id="worstsongs">Worst Songs</h2>
<hr />
<h4 id="insane">Insane</h4>
<p>A really underwhelming song with some questionable lyrics. I'll post the questionable lyrics below just b/c they're actually pretty funny.</p>
<blockquote>
  <p>Yeah we both got a car but it's different</p>
  <p>Yeah we both got a house but it's different</p>
  <p>Yeah we both got teeth but it's different</p>
  <p>I wanna see somethin' in a short skirt please</p>
  <p>I wanna see somethin' in a shirt skort please</p>
  <p>…</p>
  <p>Second verse, second verse (yay)</p>
  <p>Second verse, second verse (again)</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Truly the Motley Crew of the album but less? awful.</p>]]></description><link>https://alyssaphacker.com/music/twelve-carat-toothache</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alyssaphacker.com/music/twelve-carat-toothache</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Justin Kristensen]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 20:38:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Harry's House]]></title><description><![CDATA[<h2 id="bestsongs">Best Songs</h2>
<hr />
<h4 id="musicforasushirestaurant">Music For a Sushi Restaurant</h4>
<p>The instrumental is quite good, the acapella makes it even better. 
However, the exciting intro is almost a bit much for the underwhelming vocals. 
The scatting also feels a bit out of place? 
The instrumental more than makes up for both of these points, though.</p>
<h4 id="latenighttalking">Late Night Talking</h4>
<p>The vocal style used in this song is much better than <em>Music For a Sushi Restaurant</em>. 
The instrumental is cheery and the chorus is really catchy. 
The outro with the lyrics, "<em>All This. Late Night. Talking.</em>" made the song really stand out.</p>
<h4 id="asitwas">As It Was</h4>
<p>Fantastic song. 
Cheery upbeat drum, guitar, and synth instrumental. 
Vocals and lyrics were really well done. 
I can see why this was put out as a single before the album's eventual release.</p>
<h4 id="littlefreak">Little Freak</h4>
<p>A slower, but good song. 
Light acoustic guitar and very light drum track. 
The layering of the vocals and the melody brings this song together.</p>
<h4 id="daydreaming">Daydreaming</h4>
<p>A great instrumental, the vocal layering with the piano near the end of the song makes it pop, although the chorus was shy of "catchy".</p>
<h4 id="keepdriving">Keep Driving</h4>
<p>A nice melody, heartwarming lyrics, good flow. 
Definitely feels like a cold winter day with the heat on in the car.</p>
<h4 id="loveofmylife">Love Of My Life</h4>
<p>A perfect outro to the album. 
Dramatic synth and melody along with Harry's very up-front vocals and lyrics make this song really pop out from the rest.</p>
<h2 id="okaysongs">Okay Songs</h2>
<hr />
<h4 id="grapejuice">Grapejuice</h4>
<p>A slower song, although not perfect, does have a good guitar rift near the ending that makes up for the feeling of 'something's missing' on this track.</p>
<h4 id="daylight">Daylight</h4>
<p>A shorter song with heavy guitar and drums. 
The vocal style is light and wispy during the chorus, but overall the song was pretty forgettable.</p>
<h4 id="matilda">Matilda</h4>
<p>Based on the book/movie adaptation. 
This track is good, but barebones as well (some would argue that this track is probably better the way it is, and for the most part I agree). 
This track consists of only Harry's vocals, an acoustic guitar, and near the end, a piano.
Probably one of the better songs in this category, but just shy of being in the best songs list.</p>
<h4 id="satellite">Satellite</h4>
<p>Slower song in the beginning but ramps up towards the end. 
Overall, it wasn't that memorable.</p>
<h2 id="worstsongs">Worst Songs</h2>
<hr />
<h4 id="cinema">Cinema</h4>
<p>A funkier song, with underwhelming vocals as well as underwhelming and even cringe-y lyrics. 
Specifically, "<em>Do you think I'm cool, too?</em>" 
Not sure why, but it just rubs me the wrong way. 
Overall, the song feels unfinished with the very large pause between the chorus and the bridge.</p>
<h4 id="boyfriends">Boyfriends</h4>
<p>Another barebones song w/ acoustic guitar and Harry's layered vocals. 
The reversed vocals in the beginning were an…interesting? choice. 
The melody isn't bad but the song in general is very underwhelming and probably one of the weaker tracks on the album.</p>]]></description><link>https://alyssaphacker.com/music/harrys-house</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alyssaphacker.com/music/harrys-house</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Justin Kristensen]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 03:03:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fine Line]]></title><description><![CDATA[<h2 id="bestsongs">Best Songs</h2>
<hr />
<h4 id="golden">Golden</h4>
<p>An up-beat song with an extremely catchy chorus.
Harry's vocals stand out very prominently and are used to their full potential.
Absolutely fantastic guitar, with an interesting choice of "<em>Golden, golden, golden, golden…</em>" in the bridge.</p>
<h4 id="watermelonsugar">Watermelon Sugar</h4>
<p>A classic. 
Very light guitar in the introduction with just enough reverb on Harry's vocals.
The trumpets are a fantastic addition to the chorus.
The almost hypnotic vocals "<em>I just wanna taste it, I just wanna taste it</em>" really add to the bridge and outro.</p>
<h4 id="adoreyou">Adore You</h4>
<p>A simple song while also being one hell of an earworm.
The layered vocals on the chorus are arguably the strongest on this track.
The guitar solo near the last quarter of the song is fantastic when layered with the "<em>It's the only thing I'll ever do</em>".
Easily one of the best tracks on the album.</p>
<h4 id="lightsup">Lights Up</h4>
<p>While "Adore You" was one of the best tracks on the album due to its catchiness, "Lights Up" is easily one of the more unique tracks on the album.
Harry's vocals are much wispier on this track but are also bold and hypnotic during the chorus and outro.
The choir is especially mind-blowing during the bridges between verse and chorus.
The production is amazing and highlights every piece of instrumentation this song has to offer.</p>
<h4 id="falling">Falling</h4>
<p>A slower song with a piano as the main melody.
The lyrics and vocals by Harry are especially powerful on this track.
The lyrics, "<em>What if I'm someone I don't want around?</em>" are especially confessional.</p>
<h4 id="she">She</h4>
<p>A slower song, but unlike its predecessor, "To Be So Lonely," has a good rhythm and is packed more instrumentally.
The guitar (and especially the solo) is, as always, top-notch and the vocalistic blending in some quieter parts of the song really make this song unique.</p>
<h4 id="sunflowervol6">Sunflower, Vol. 6</h4>
<p>A funky, almost hippie-like song with some amazing lyrics.
Definitely a song you can listen to while roaming in a field of sunflowers on a sunny day.
The scatting in the outro makes this song yet another unique track on this album.</p>
<h4 id="canyonmoon">Canyon Moon</h4>
<p>A feel-good song with lyrics reminiscing about love and the amazing feeling of going home after a long time of being away.</p>
<h4 id="fineline">Fine Line</h4>
<p>A longer song and excellent outro to the album.
Starts off with a simple acoustic guitar with Harry's mirrored vocals and eventually builds up to an orchestral finale.</p>
<h2 id="okaysongs">Okay Songs</h2>
<hr />
<h4 id="cherry">Cherry</h4>
<p>A slower song with a banjo as the main melody.
Overall, a good song but lacks in comparison to what came before it.
Almost sounds like it would belong in an indie/romance film.</p>
<h2 id="worstsongs">Worst Songs</h2>
<hr />
<h4 id="tobesolonely">To Be So Lonely</h4>
<p>A slow song with a ukulele as the main melody to go with Harry's bare vocals.
The majority of the song is bare but is also lacking.
The lyrics seem to be mostly about denial of alcoholism, which almost goes back on what the previous track, "Falling," was trying to confess.</p>
<h4 id="treatpeoplewithkindness">Treat People With Kindness</h4>
<p>Probably one of the worst tracks on the record.
Reminds me of Michael Jackson's "Can You Feel It," but if the choir was lacking cohesion with the main melody.</p>]]></description><link>https://alyssaphacker.com/music/fine-line</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://alyssaphacker.com/music/fine-line</guid><category><![CDATA[Harry Styles]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Justin Kristensen]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 06:11:32 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>